Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6 5583/6
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- H. J. Heinz Company, 1953-1960 (Box 19B, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The 57 News, 1953-1960 (Box 19B, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.36 (1953)-v.43 (1960)
- General Electric Company, Erie Works, 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Erie Works), 1934-1939 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Author: News Bureau
    Notes: v.15 (1934)- v.20 (1939). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Erie Works, 1940-1942 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Erie Works), 1940-1942 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21 (1940)- v.23 (1942). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Erie Works, 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Erie Works), 1943-1945 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.24 (1943)- v.26 (1945). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Erie Works, 1946-1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Erie Works), 1946-1948 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27 (1946)- v.29 (1948). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Erie Works, 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Erie Works), 1949-1951 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    Notes: January 7, 1949-December 28, 1951. Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Switchgear Divisions, 1948-1950 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Switchgear Divisions), 1948-1950 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Author: General Electric Company, Switchgear Divisions
    Notes: v.26 (1948)-v.28 (1950). Bound volume.
- Dravo Corporation, 1949-1955 (Box 22A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Dravo Slant, 1949-1955 (Box 22A, Folder 1)
    Author: Dravo Corporation
    Notes: v.1 (1949:Jan.)-v.7 (1955:Oct.). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Switchgear Divisions, 1957-1959 (Box 22A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Switchgear Divisions), 1957-1959 (Box 22A, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.35 (1957)-v.37 (1959). Bound volume.
- Lever Brothers Company, 1948-1950 (Box 22A, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Lever Standard, 1948-1950 (Box 22A, Folder 4)
    Author: Lever Brothers Company
    Notes: v.20:no.2 (1948:Feb.)-v.22:no.11 (1950:Dec.). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Switchgear Divisions, 1951-1953 (Box 22B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Switchgear Divisions), 1951-1953 (Box 22B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.29 (1951)-v.31 (1953). Bound volume.
- General Electric Company, Switchgear Divisions, 1954-1956 (Box 22B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: General Electric News (Switchgear Divisions), 1954-1956 (Box 22B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.32 (1954)-v.34 (1956). Bound volume.
- Lockheed-California Company, 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Lockheed Star, 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Author: Lockheed-California Company
    Notes: v.17 (1950)- v.24 (1957). Bound volume.
- Lockheed-California Company, 1958-1962 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Lockheed Star, 1958-1962 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.25 (1958)- v.29 (1962). Bound volume.
- Lockheed-California Company, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Lockheed Star, 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.30 (1963)- v.32 (1965). Bound volume.
- Lockheed-California Company, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Lockheed Star, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.33 (1966)- v.35 (1968). Bound volume.
- Lockheed-California Company, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Lockheed Star, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.36 (1969)- v.37 (1970). Bound volume.
- New Departure Manufacturing, 1917-1925 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: New Departure News, 1917-1925 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    Author: New Departure Manufacturing
    Notes: v.1 (1971:Mar.)-v.2:no.50 (1925:Sept.). Bound volume.
- New Departure Manufacturing, 1925-1929 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: New Departure News, 1925-1929 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.51 (1925:Oct.)-v.2:no.99 (1929:Oct.). Bound volume.
- PERB (New York State Public Employment Relations Board), 1969; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: New York State Public Employment Board (Releases), 1969; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Author: PERB (New York State Public Employment Relations Board)
    Notes: January-June, 1969. Bound volume.
- PERB (New York State Public Employment Relations Board), 1969; Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New York State Public Employment Board (Releases), 1969; Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Notes: July-December, 1969. Bound volume.
- PERB (New York State Public Employment Relations Board), 1970; Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: New York State Public Employment Board (Releases), 1970; Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Notes: January-June, 1970. Bound volume.
- PERB (New York State Public Employment Relations Board), 1968; Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New York State Public Employment Board (Releases), 1968; Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Notes: July-December, 1968. Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1952-1954 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Pennsy, 1952-1954 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Author: Pennsylvania Railroad Company
    Notes: v.1 (1952)-v.3 (1954). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Pennsy, 1955-1956 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.4 (1955)-v.5 (1956). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Pennsy, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6 (1957)-v.10 (1961). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Pennsy, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11 (1962)- v.13 (1964). Bound volume.
- American Optical Company, 1923-1927 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Wellsworth Life, 1923-1927 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Author: American Optical Company
    Notes: no.7 (1923)- no.11 (1927). Bound volume.
- Lever Brothers Company, 1955-1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Lever Standard, 1955-1963 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.27:no.1 (1955:Mar.)-v.35:no.10 (1963:Dec.). Bound volume.
- Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Pennsy, 1964-1968 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Notes: December, 1964-January, 1968. Bound volume.
- Associated Silk Workers of America, 1929-1930 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Silk Worker, 1929-1930 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Associated Silk Workers of America
    Notes: April, 1929-February, 1930. Bound volume.
- DuPont Industries, 1944-1948 (Box 27A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Chamber Works News, 1944-1948 (Box 27A, Folder 1)
    Author: DuPont Industries
    Notes: v.8:no.5 (1944:Apr. 7) - v.11:no.26 (1948:Jan. 23). Bound volume.
- DuPont Industries, 1948-1951 (Box 27A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Chamber Works News, 1948-1951 (Box 27A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1948:Feb. 6) - v.14:no.26 (1951:Jan. 19). Bound volume.
- UAW., 1955-1958 (Box 27B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 719 News, 1955-1958 (Box 27B, Folder 1)
    Author: UAW. Local 719
    Notes: v.4:no.27 (1955:July/Aug.) - v.5:no.3 (1958:Apr./May). Bound volume.
- Chase Manhattan Bank, 1957-1965 (Box 27B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Chase Manhattan News, 1957-1965 (Box 27B, Folder 2)
    Author: Chase Manhattan Bank
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1957:Nov.) - v.9:no.12 (1965:Dec.). Bound volume.
- Chase Manhattan Bank, 1966-1970 (Box 27B, Folder 3)
- DuPont Industries, 1937-1943 (Box 28A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Dyeworks News, 1937-1943 (Box 28A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1937:Feb. 18) - v.6:no.26 (1943:Jan. 29). Bound volume.
- DuPont Industries, 1943-1944 (Box 28A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Dyeworks News, 1943-1944 (Box 28A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1943:Feb. 12) - v.8:no.4 (1944:Mar. 24). Bound volume.
  - Item 2: General Welfare News-Advocate, 1938-1941 (Box 28A, Folder 2)
    Author: General Welfare Federation of America
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1938:Mar. 14) - v.3:no.52 (1941:Mar. 3). Bound volume.
- General Welfare Federation of America, 1938-1947 (Box 28A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: General Welfare Reporter, 1945-1947 (Box 28A, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.11:no.18 (1945:Mar. 13) - v.11:no.45 (1947:Jan.). Bound volume.
- Federated Press, 1931; Publication (Box 28A, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor's News, 1931; Publication (Box 28A, Folder 4)
    Author: Federated Press
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1931: July 4) - v.21:no.18 (1931:Oct. 31). Bound volume
- Standard Oil Company of New Jersey, 1929-1944 (Box 28B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The "Standard" Refiner, 1929-1934 (Box 28B, Folder 1)
    Author: Standard Oil Company of New Jersey
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1929:Jan. 5) - v.6:no.6 (1934:June). Bound volume. Bound with following title: The Esso Refiner.
  - Item 2: The Esso Refiner, 1934-1944 (Box 28B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1934:July) - v.16:no.25 (1944:Dec. 22). Bound volume. Bound with previous title: The "Standard" Refiner.
- Federated Press, 1929-1931 (Box 28B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labor's News, 1929-1931 (Box 28B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.16:no.22 (1929:Mar. 14) - v.20:no.26 (1931:June 27). Bound volume
- Norton Company, 1914-1927 (Box 29A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Norton Spirit, 1914-1927 (Box 29A, Folder 1)
    Author: Norton Company
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1914:Dec.) - v.12:no.28 (1927:June 15). Bound volume
- Norton Company, 1927-1930 (Box 29A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Norton Spirit, 1927-1930 (Box 29A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1927:July 1) - v.16:no.11/12 (1930:Nov./Dec.). Bound volume.
- Norton Company, 1943-1955 (Box 29A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Norton Spirit, 1943-1955 (Box 29A, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.29:no.6 (1943:Jan.) - v.42:no.3 (1955:Oct.). Bound volume.
- CWA (Communication Workers of America), 1950-1951 (Box 29B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Michigan Communication Worker, 1950-1951 (Box 29B, Folder 1)
    Author: Michigan Division 15
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1950:Apr.) - v.1:no.10 (1951:Mar.). Bound volume.
- NUR (National Union of Railwaymen), 1950-1952 (Box 29B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Railway Review, 1950-1952 (Box 29B, Folder 2)
    Author: NUR (National Union of Railwaymen)
    Notes: no.3757 (1950:Sep. 8) - no.3877 (1952:Dec. 26). Bound volume.
- Fairchild News Service, 1936; Publication (Box 30A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Retailing (Executive Edition), 1936; Publication (Box 30A, Folder 1)
    Author: Fairchild News Service
    Notes: v.8 (1936). Bound volume.
- Fairchild News Service, 1937; Publication (Box 30A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Retailing (Executive Edition), 1937; Publication (Box 30A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9 (1937). Bound volume.
- Fairchild News Service, 1938; Publication (Box 30B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Retailing (Executive Edition), 1938; Publication (Box 30B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.10 (1938). Bound volume.
- Fairchild News Service, 1939; Publication (Box 30B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Retailing (Executive Edition), 1939; Publication (Box 30B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.11 (1939). Bound volume.
- Fairchild News Service, 1940; Publication (Box 31A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Retailing (Executive Edition), 1940; Publication (Box 31A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12 (1940). Bound volume.
- John A. Roebling's Sons Company, 1949-1958 (Box 31A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Roebling Record, 1949-1958 (Box 31A, Folder 2)
    Author: John A. Roebling's Sons Company
    Notes: v.2:no.10 (1949:July 1) - v.11:no.6 (1958:Mar.). Bound volume. Bound with On Guard for Roebling Safety.
  - Item 2: On Guard for Roebling Safety, 1949-1954 (Box 31A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1949:June) - v.6:no.1 (1954:Feb.). Bound volume. Bound with Roebling Record.
- John A. Roebling's Sons Company, 1949-1954 (Box 31A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Roebling Record, 1949-1958 (Box 31A, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: On Guard for Roebling Safety, 1949-1954 (Box 31A, Folder 2)
- Swift and Company, 1932-1940 (Box 31B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Swift Arrow, 1932-1940 (Box 31B, Folder 1)
    Author: Swift and Company
    Notes: v.12:no.8 (1932:Feb. 11) - v.19:no.12 (1940:Apr.). Bound volume.
- Swift and Company, 1940-1946 (Box 31B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Swift Arrow, 1940-1946 (Box 31B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.1 (1940:May) - v.25:no.12 (1946:Apr.). Bound volume.
- Swift and Company, 1946-1947 (Box 32A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Swift Arrow, 1946-1947 (Box 32A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.26:no.1 (1946:May) - v.27:no.3 (1947:July). Bound volume.
- Dyers Federation, 1948-1949 (Box 32A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Textile Dyer, 1948-1949 (Box 32A, Folder 2)
    Author: Dyers Federation
    Notes: October, 1948 - November, 1949. Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1945; Publication (Box 32B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1945; Publication (Box 32B, Folder 1)
    Author: Trade Union Courier Publishing
    Notes: v.10:no.11 (1945:May 28) - v.10:no.26 (1945:Dec. 24). Bound volume
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1946; Publication (Box 32B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1946; Publication (Box 32B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.11:no.1 (1946:Jan. 7) - v.11:no.13 (1946:June 24). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1946; Publication (Box 33A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1946; Publication (Box 33A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.11:no.14 (1946:July 8) - v.11:no.26 (1946:Dec. 23). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1947; Publication (Box 33A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1947; Publication (Box 33A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1947:Jan. 13) - v.12:no.13 (1947:June 30). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1947; Publication (Box 33A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1947; Publication (Box 33A, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.14 (1947:July 14) - v.12:no.26 (1947:Dec. 29). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1948; Publication (Box 33B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1948; Publication (Box 33B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1948:Jan. 12) - v.13:no.14 (1948:July 12). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1948; Publication (Box 33B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1948; Publication (Box 33B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.15 (1948:July 26) - v.13:no.24 (1948:Dec. 6). Bound volume
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1949; Publication (Box 33B, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1949; Publication (Box 33B, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (1949:Jan. 3) - v.14:no.12 (1949:June 12). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1950; Publication (Box 34A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1950; Publication (Box 34A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.15:no.1 (1950:Jan. 16) - v.15:no.12 (1950:June 19). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1950-1951 (Box 34A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1950-1951 (Box 34A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.15:no.13 (1950:July 3) - v.15:no.26 (1951:Jan. 1). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1951; Publication (Box 34A, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1951; Publication (Box 34A, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.1 (1951:Jan. 15) - v.16:no.13 (1951:July 2). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1949-1950 (Box 34B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1949-1950 (Box 34B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14:no.14 (1949:July 18) - v.14:no.26 (1950:Jan. 2). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1951-1952 (Box 34B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1951-1952 (Box 34B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.16:no.14 (1951:July 30) v.16:no.26 (1952:Jan. 14). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1952-1953 (Box 34B, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1952-1953 (Box 34B, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1952:Jan. 28) - v.17:no.26 (1953:Feb. 25). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1953-1954 (Box 35A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1953-1954 (Box 35A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1953:Mar. 11) - v.18:no.25 (1954:Feb. 17). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1954-1955 (Box 35A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1954-1955 (Box 35A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.1 (1954:Mar. 3) - v.19:no.25 (1955: Feb. 2). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1955-1956 (Box 35B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1955-1956 (Box 35B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.1 (1955:Feb. 16) - v.20:no.25 (1956:Feb. 10). Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1956-1957 (Box 35B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1956-1957 (Box 35B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.1 (1956:Feb. 24) - v.20:no.25 (1957:Mar. 1). Actually v.21: entire volume misnumbered. Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1957-1958 (Box 36A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1957-1958 (Box 36A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1957: Mar. 15) - v.21:no.22 (1958:Jan. 10). Actually v.22: entire volume misnumbered. Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1958; Publication (Box 36A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1958; Publication (Box 36A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.21:no.22 (1958:Jan. 10) - v.22:no.24 (1958:Dec. 19). Actually v.22/23: Entire volume misnumbered. Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1959; Publication (Box 36B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1959; Publication (Box 36B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.23:no.1 (1959:Jan. 2) - v.25:no.25 (1959:Dec. 18). Volume number corrected with v.24:no.2; v.24:no.17 and subsequent misnumbered v.25. Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1960-1962 (Box 36B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1960-1962 (Box 36B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26 (1960) - v.28 (1962). Actually v.25-27: All three volumes misnumbered. Bound volume.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1986-1988 (Box 37A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1986-1988 (Box 37A, Folder 1)
    Notes: Loose issues. Most volume numbers for these years are printed as invalid strings of Roman numerals.
- Trade Union Courier Publishing, 1989-1992 (Box 37B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade Union Courier, 1989-1992 (Box 37B, Folder 1)
- Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America, 1945; Publication (Box 38A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union Voice, 1945; Publication (Box 38A, Folder 1)
    Author: Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1945:Jan. 7) - v.1:no.26 (1945:Dec. 23). Bound volume.
- Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America, 1947-1948 (Box 38A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Union Voice, 1947-1948 (Box 38A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1947:Jan. 5) - v.4:no.25 (1948:Dec. 5). Bound volume.
- Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America, 1946; Publication (Box 38B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union Voice, 1946; Publication (Box 38B, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1946:Jan. 6) - v.2:no.26 (1946:Dec. 22). Bound volume.
- Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America, 1949-1950 (Box 38B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Union Voice, 1949-1950 (Box 38B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1949:Jan. 2) - v.6:no.27 (1950:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
- Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America, 1951-1952 (Box 39A, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union Voice, 1951-1952 (Box 39A, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1951:Jan. 14) - v.8:no.26 (1952:Dec. 28). Bound volume.
- Distributing, Processing and Office Workers of America, 1953-1954 (Box 39A, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Union Voice, 1953-1954 (Box 39A, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1953:Jan. 11) - v.10:no.10 (1954:May 16). Bound volume.
- UERMWA (United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America), 1946-1949 (Box 39B, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: United Front, 1946-1949 (Box 39B, Folder 1)
    Author: Westinghouse Industrial Union, Local 202
    Notes: v.13 (1946) - v.16 (1949). Bound volume.
- UERMWA (United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America), 1950-1955 (Box 39B, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: United Front, 1950-1955 (Box 39B, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17 (1950) - v.23 (1955). Bound volume.
- British Institute of Management, 1948-1950 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: BIM Management Bulletin, 1948-1950 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    Author: British Institute of Management
    Notes: no.1 (1948:Dec.) - no.7 (1950:Feb.). Bound volume.
- Texaco; The Texas Pipeline Company, 1926-1930 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Bit and Tongs, 1926-1930 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    Author: Texaco
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1926:June) - v.4:no.9/10 (1930:Feb./Mar.). Bound volume.
- Black and Decker Manufacturing, 1952-1959 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Blade, 1952-1959 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Author: Black and Decker Manufacturing
    Notes: v.13 (1953) - v.18 (1959). Bound volume.
- Black and Decker Manufacturing, 1960-1967 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Blade, 1960-1967 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.19 (1960) - v.26 (1967). Bound volume.
- American Brake Shoe Company, 1949-1957 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Brake Shoe News, 1949-1957 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Author: American Brake Shoe Company
- CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations), 1952-1954 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: CIO World Affairs Bulletin, 1952-1954 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Author: CIO (Congress of Industrial Organizations)
    Notes: v.1:no.5 (1952:Feb.) - v.1:no.1 (1954:April/May.). Bound volume.
- U. S. Department of Labor, 1934-1937 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Changes During (Month) in Different Types of Public and Private Relief in Urban Areas, 1934-1937 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Author: Children's Bureau
    Notes: December 15, 1934 - March 29, 1937. Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Management Record, 1939-1941 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.1 (1939) - v.3 (1941). Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1942-1943 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Management Record, 1942-1943 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.4 (1942) - v.5 (1943). Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Management Record, 1944-1945 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6 (1944) - v.7 (1945). Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1946-1947 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Management Record, 1946-1947 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.8 (1946) - v.9 (1947). Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1948-1949 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Management Record, 1948-1949 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10 (1948) - v.11 (1949). Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Management Record, 1950-1951 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.12 (1951) - v.13 (1951). Bound volume.
- National Industrial Conference Board, 1952-1953 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Conference Board Management Record, 1952-1953 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.14 (1952) - v.15 (1953). Bound volume.
- Connecticut Business and Industry Association, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1972-1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.50:no.9 (1972:Sept.) - v.51:no.12 (1973:Dec.). Bound volume
- Connecticut Business and Industry Association, 1974; Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Connecticut Industry, 1974; Publication (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.52 (1974). Bound volume.
- Migrant Legal Action Program, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Earthbond, 1975-1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Author: Migrant Legal Action Program
    Notes: v.4 (1975) - v.5 (1977). Bound volume.
- Religion and Labor Foundation, 1948-1957 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Economic Justice, 1948-1957 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Author: Religion and Labor Foundation
    Notes: v.16:no.6 (1948:Feb.) - v.25:no.9 (1957:June/July). Bound volume.
- Edison Lamp Works. General Electric., 1922-1925 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Edison Lamp Works News, 1922-1925 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Author: Edison Lamp Works. General Electric.
    Notes: v.3 (1922) - v.6 (1925). Bound volume.
- Commonwealth Edison, 1923-1926 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Edison Round Table, 1923-1926 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Author: Commonwealth Edison
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1923:Jan. 13) - v.9:no.24 (1925:Dec. 31); v.18:no.1 (1926: Jan. 15) - v.18:no.24 (1926:Dec. 31). Bound volume.
- Commonwealth Edison, 1927-1929 (Box 43, Folder 1)